A Guide to the Papers of The World Affairs Council of Hampton Roads 1968-2000
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 1990s
  - Programs and Events
    - WAC and City of Portsmouth Event - W. Nathaniel Howell, Jr.,Former U.S. Ambassador to Kuwait February 4, 1991 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - WAC and OCU Event - Dr. Jagdish N. Bhagwati, Columbia University March 27, 1991 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - WAC and ODU Event - Edward J. Perkins, Director General of the Foreign Service and Director of Personnel April 5, 1991 (Box-folder 15:14)
    - WAC Event - Emmanuel N. Pelaez, Ambassador from the Philippines June 6, 1991 (Box-folder 15:15)
    - WAC, The Cyprus Benevolent Society of Tidewater, The Hellenic American Communities of Norfolk, Virginia Beach, and Newport News, VA., and ODU Event - Androula G. Vassilou, First Lady of Cyprus July 27, 1991 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - WAC Event - Gerald L. Baliles, Former Governor of Virginia September 23, 1991 (Box-folder 15:17)
    - WAC Event - Jacques Andreani, Ambassador from France October 17, 1991 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - WAC Event - Elisabeth Rehn, Minister of Defense from Finland October 29, 1991 (Box-folder 15:19)
    - WAC Event - Don Oberdorfer, Diplomatic Correspondent for the Washington Post January 9, 1992 (Box-folder 15:20)
    - WAC Event - Rita Klimova, Ambassador from Czechoslovakia February 6, 1992 (Box-folder 15:21)
    - WAC Event - Peter P. Dyvig, Ambassador from Denmark (cancelled) February 13, 1992 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - WAC and Town-N-Gown Event - Adm. Dieter Wellershoff, Former Chief of Defense of the German Armed Forces March 11, 1992 (Box-folder 15:23)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Robert E. Fritz May 21, 1992 (Box-folder 15:24)
    - WAC Event - Zhu Qizhen, Ambassador from the People’s Republic of China June 25, 1992 (Box-folder 15:25)
    - WAC and ODU Event - Hong-Choo Hyun, Ambassador from the Republic of Korea September 10, 1992 (Box-folder 15:26)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Stanley Kalpage, Ambassador from Sri Lanka October 22, 1992 (Box-folder 15:27)
    - WAC Event - Michael Hornblow, Chief Deputy of Mission, American Embassy, Warsaw, Poland Dec. 15, 1992 (Box-folder 15:28)
    - WAC and WHRO Event - Dr. Claus Kleber, Washington Correspondent for ARD German Television February 11, 1993 (Box-folder 15:29)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College - Boris Biancheri, Vice Consul of Italy February 18, 1993 (Box-folder 15:30)
    - WAC and Internes Hispano Event - Alejandro Carrillo-Castro, Mexican Ambassador to the Organization of American States (cancelled) March 25, 1993 (Box-folder 15:31)
    - WAC Event - Diana E. McMeekin, Executive Vice President, African Wildlife Foundation April 27, 1993 (Box-folder 15:32)
    - WAC Event - Anna Chennault, President, TAC International, Inc., Chairman, Council for International Cooperation May 13, 1993 (Box-folder 15:33)
    - WAC and ODU Event - Oleh H. Bilorus, Ambassador from Ukraine June 10, 1993 (Box-folder 15:34)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College - Donald P. Gregg, Chairman, The Korean Society June 16, 1993 (Box-folder 15:35)
    - WAC Event - Lowell Bruce Laingen, President, American Academy of Diplomacy September 23, 1993 (Box-folder 15:36)
    - WAC Event - Morton I. Abramowitz, President, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace October 14, 1993 (Box-folder 15:37)
    - WAC Event - Donald F. McHenry, University Research Professor of Diplomacy and International Affairs, Georgetown University November 2, 1993 (Box-folder 15:38)
    - WAC Event - Alexander Borg Olivier, United Nations Department of Humanitarian Affairs December 7, 1993 (Box-folder 15:39)
    - WAC and WHRO/WHRV-FM Event - James Fallows, Washington Editor, The Atlantic Monthly January 19, 1994 (Box-folder 15:40)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Simon Serfaty, Center for Strategic and International Studies February 9, 1994 (Box-folder 15:41)
    - WAC Event - Paul W. Jacobs, First Secretary, Embassy of South Africa May 12, 1994 (Box-folder 15:42)
    - WAC and ODU Event - Jeffrey Garten, U.S. Under Secretary of Commerce for International Trade September 22, 1994 (Box-folder 15:43)
    - WAC Event - Richard Burt, Chairman, International Equity Partners September 29, 1994 (Box-folder 15:44)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Dimitri K. Simes, President, Nixon Center for Peace and Freedom November 17, 1994 (Box-folder 15:45)
    - WAC Event - S.R. Nathan, Ambassador from Singapore December 1, 1994 (Box-folder 15:46)
    - WAC, WHRO/WHRV-FM and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Robert Siegel, Host, National Public Radio’s All Things Considered January 12, 1995 (Box-folder 15:47)
    - WAC Event - Raul Ch. Rabe, Ambassador from the Philippines February 16, 1995 (Box-folder 15:48)
    - WAC Event - 25th Anniversary March 23, 1995 (Box-folder 15:49)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Harry Harding, Dean, Elliott School of International Affairs, George Washington University May 18, 1995 (Box-folder 15:50)
    - WAC and EVMS Event - Laurie Garrett, Author and Journalist June 15, 1995 (Box-folder 15:51)
    - WAC Event - Walter B. Slocombe, Under Secretary of Defense General John Sheehan, USMC, Supreme Allied Commander, Atlantic September 28, 1995 (Box-folder 15:52)
    - WAC Event - Lawrence S. Eagleburger, Former Secretary of Defense October 23, 1995 (Box-folder 15:53)
    - WAC Event - Peter Tarnoff, Under Secretary of State for Political Affairs November 2, 1995 (Box-folder 15:54)
    - WAC Event - Paul D. Wolfowitz, Dean, The Paul H. Nitze School of Advanced International Studies, Johns Hopkins University December 14, 1995 (Box-folder 15:55)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Nigel Holloway, Washington Bureau Chief, The Far Eastern Economic Review January 17, 1996 (Box-folder 15:56)
    - WAC Event - Werner Fronos, President, The Population Institute March 14, 1996 (Box-folder 15:57)
    - WAC Event - Hulmut Tuerk, Ambassador from Austria May 21, 1996 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - WAC Event - U.S. State Department, Foreign Policy Town Meeting June 20, 1996 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Li Daoyu, Ambassador from the People’s Republic of China October 9, 1996 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - WAC and Alliance Francaise Event - Francis Bujon De L'Estang, Ambassador from France November 6, 1996 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - WAC Event - Carlo Jagmetti, Ambassador from Switzerland November 21, 1996 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Gyorgy Banlaki, Ambassador from Hungary December 12, 1996 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - WAC and Town-N-Gown Event - Maestra JoAnn Falletta, Music Director of the Virginia Symphony Orchestra January 26, 1997 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - WAC Event - Nuzhet Kandemir, Ambassador of the Republic of Turkey February 28, 1997 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Dr. Mohammed S. Al-Sabah, Ambassador of the State of Kuwait (cancelled) March 19, 1997 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - WAC and Canon Virginia, Inc. - Ichiro Fujisaki, Political Minister, Embassy of Japan May 29, 1997 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Kun Woo Park, Ambassador of the Republic of Korea July 2, 1997 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - WAC and Christopher Newport University Event - Dr. Sergei Khrushchev, Senior Fellow, Thomas J. Watson, Jr. Institute for International Studies, Brown University September 22, 1997 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - WAC Event - Andre Adam, Ambassador from Belgium October 23, 1997 (Box-folder 16:13)
    - WAC, ODU and Town-n-Gown Event - John Keegan, OBE, Military Historian, Educator and Journalist November 6, 1997 (Box-folder 16:14)
    - WAC and Prudential Securities, Inc. Event - Stephen F. Auth, Senior Managing Director of Prudential Investments December 10, 1997 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - WAC and Virginia Wesleyan College Event - Stephen S.F. Chen,Taipei Economic and Cultural Representative January 27, 1998 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - WAC Event - Regis P. Arslanian, Minister-Counselor of the Brazilian Embassy February 18, 1998 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - WAC Event- Matthew F. McHugh, Counselor to the President of the World Bank March 12, 1998 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - WAC and Christopher Newport University Event - Admiral Stansfield Turner, U.S.N. (Ret.), Former Director of the C.I.A. March 23, 1998 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - WAC, Virginia Wesleyan College and The United Jewish Federation of Tidewater Event - Dr. Michael Bar-Zohar, Author, Biographer and Professor May 12, 1998 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - WAC Event - June 11, 1998 - Dr. William B. Quandt, Middle East/Oil Expert June 11, 1998 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - WAC Event - Bill Keller September 17, 1998 (Box-folder 16:22)
    - WAC Event - Donald D. Holt October 21, 1998 (Box-folder 16:23)
    - WAC Event - Werner Ablass November 12, 1998 (Box-folder 16:24)
    - WAC Event - Dr. David Satcher November 19, 1998 (Box-folder 16:25)
    - WAC Event - Karen Kasmauski January 21, 1999 (Box-folder 16:26)
    - WAC Event - World Quest January 28, 1999 (Box-folder 16:27)
    - WAC Event - Charles Maynes February 11, 1999 (Box-folder 16:28)
    - WAC Event - H.E. Alhaji Hassan Adamu March 18, 1999 (Box-folder 16:29)
    - WAC Event - H.E. Jurgen Chrobog April 14, 1999 (Box-folder 16:30)
    - WAC Event - Sotirios C. Zackheos May 20, 1999 (Box-folder 16:31)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Nedzib Sacirbey June 17, 1999 (Box-folder 16:32)
    - WAC Event - H.E. Raymond A. J. Chretien June 30, 1999 (Box-folder 16:33)
    - WAC Event - William G. Hyland September 30, 1999 (Box-folder 16:34)
    - WAC Event - H.E. Farid Abboud October 14, 1999 (Box-folder 16:35)
    - WAC Event- Dr. Michael J. Mazaar November 17, 1999 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Miscellaneous WAC Events undated (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Other Events - Non-WAC undated (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Budget and Finance
    - Agent - C. Arthur Robinson undated (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Audits 1990-94 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Audits 1995-99 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - National Council of World Affairs Organizations Bi-Annual Financial Survey Report October 1994 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Taxes 1990s (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Taxes Records 1995 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - Taxes Records 1996 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Taxes Records 1997 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Taxes 1999 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - Treasurer’s Report 1990-94 (Box-folder 17:13)
    - Treasurer’s Report, (I) 1995-96 (Box-folder 17:14)
    - Treasurer’s Report, (II) 1995-96 (Box-folder 17:15)
    - Treasurer’s Report, (I) 1996-97 (Box-folder 17:16)
    - Treasurer’s Report, (II) 1996-97 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Treasurer’s Report, (III) 1996-97 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Treasurer’s Report 1997-1998 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Publicity and Publications
    - Publicity Committee undated (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1990s (Box-folder 18:5)
    - WAC Newsletter August 23, 1997 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Great Decisions Magazine 1992 Edition (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Association for International Practical Training: 1994 Annual Report 1994 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Foreign Policy Association: Newsletter Spring 1994 and April 1995 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Press Releases/Publicity 1998-1999 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Oversized Newspaper Articles undated (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Photos
    - Kaufman Hall Photos (I) 1990 (Box-folder 18:12)
    - Kaufman Hall Photos (II) 1990 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - Norfolk Airport Hilton Photos 1990 (Box-folder 18:14)
    - Photos for Newspaper Articles 1997-1999 (Box-folder 18:15)
    - Webb Center Photos 1990 (Box-folder 18:16)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 19:1)
- 2000s
  - Organization
    - WAC Bylaws, articles and meeting minutes 1969 - 2003 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Business
    - Advisory Council undated (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Annual Report 2000-2001 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Annual Report- 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Annual Report- 2002-2003 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Annual Report- 2003-2004 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Annual Report- 2004-2005 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Annual Report- 2006 2006 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Board Retreat- 2000-2001 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Board Retreat 2003 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Board Retreat 2004 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Board Retreat 2005 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - Board Retreat 2006 (Box-folder 19:14)
    - Case for Support 2000 (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Community Achievements 2002-2003 (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Corporate Sponsor Campaigns undated (Box-folder 19:17)
    - Corporate Sponsor Summaries undated (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Development Committee 2000-03 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Development Committee 2004-05 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Development: Year-End Gift Giving 2004 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Directors and Officers Insurance 2001-2004 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Education 2000- (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Education Committee undated (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Education Summaries undated (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Events for 2004 2004 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Executive Committee Meetings 2002-2003 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Executive Committee Meetings 2003-2004 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Executive Committee Meetings 2004-2005 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Finance Committee 2003-2005 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Foreign Policy Association 2004 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - General Liability Insurance 2004-2005 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Interns Fall 2004 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Interns Fall 2005 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Interns Spring 2005 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Interns Spring 2006 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Interns Summer 2005 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Leave a Legacy 2003 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Meetings/Agendas 1999-2005 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Minutes and Agendas 2000 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Minutes and Agendas 2001 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Minutes and Agendas 2002 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Minutes and Agendas 2003 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - Minutes and Agendas 2004 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Nominating Committee 2004 - 2005 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Past Conferences 2004 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Position Descriptions undated (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Potential Programs 2000 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Potential Programs 2005 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Prospects 2004-06 (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Public Relations Committee undated (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Public Relations 2000 (Box-folder 22:8)
    - Public Relations 2001 (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Recommended Speakers 2005 (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Relocation of Office undated (Box-folder 22:11)
    - Scholarships 2001 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - School Contacts 2004-2005 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Speaker Recommendations/Notes on Past Speakers undated (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Strategic Plan 2005-2008 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Update on Program Committee Topics undated (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Virginia Employment Commission's Notice of Deputy's Termination undated (Box-folder 23:6)
    - WACA undated (Box-folder 23:7)
    - WACA Directory undated (Box-folder 23:8)
    - WHRO undated (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Year-End Giving 2002 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Correspondence and Mailing
    - Bulk Mail Information 2004-2005 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Bulk Mail Information 2005-2006 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - General Correspondence 2000 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - General Correspondence 2001 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - General Correspondence 2003 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - General Correspondence 2004 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Jefferson Award Nomination 2000 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Letters of Congratulations for 35th Anniversary 2004 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Mailing Lists/Mailer Information 2003-2005 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Thank-you Letters 2000-2002 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Thank-you Letters 2003-2004 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Membership
    - Membership Database 2000-2004 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Membership Forms undated (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Membership Lists 2000 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Membership Summaries undated (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Memberships (Misc. including membership form samples from sister organizations) 2004-2006 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - New Member Lists 2002 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Program Sponsor Inserts 2000-2003 (Box-folder 24:14)
  - Programs And Events
    - Monthly Guest Lectures 2000’s (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Azalea Festival 2000 (Box-folder 24:16)
    - H.E. Kamlesh Sharma January 28, 2000 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - General Barry McCaffrey February 17, 2000 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - H.E. Geza Jeszenskzky March 14, 2000 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - H.E. Alexander Philon March 23, 2000 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Great Decisions 2000 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Charles S. Shapiro, Director, Office of Cuban-American Affairs, U.S. Department of State May18, 2000 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Dr. Gary Burtless, Brookings Institute June 8, 2000 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Liu Xiaoming, Deputy Chief of Mission, Embassy of the People's Republic of China September 14, 2000 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Dr. Stephen Blount, Director, Global Health, Center for Disease Control September 28, 2000 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - WAC, Korean Economic Institute and Christopher Newport University Event - Yang Sung-Chul, Ambassador of the Republic of Korea October 19, 2000 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Mark L. Schneider, Director, United States Peace Corps November 16, 2000 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - World Quest November 2000 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Corporate Sponsor Campaign Lunch December 2000 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - WAC and Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce Event - Dr. Mamphela Ramphele, Managing Director, The World Bank January 18, 2001 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Great Decisions 2001 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Michael Maibach and Dr. Alan Tonelson January 31, 2001 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Corporate Sponsor Campaign Lunch February 2001 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Dr. Marwan Jamil Muasher, Ambassador of the Hashmetite Kingdom of Jordon February 20, 2001 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - WAC and The Navy League of Hampton Roads Event - Sir Eldon Griffiths, National Chairman, World Affairs Councils of the United States March 9, 2001 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - H.E. Javier Ruperez April 25, 2001 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Ambassador Monteagle Stearns, American Academy of Diplomacy May 3, 2001 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission Bulletin - Taiwan May 19-25, 2001 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Paul A. Goble, Communications Director, Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty May 31, 2001 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - World War 2 Travel Program June 25, 2001 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Sir Christopher Meyer, KCMG, Ambassador of Great Britain (Cancelled due to 9/11) September 19, 2001 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Vietnam/Southeast Asia Cruise 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:14)
    - Gerald L. Baliles, Virginia's "International" October 9, 2001 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - WAC and Economics Club of Hampton Roads Event - Jeffrey E. Garten, Dean, Yale University School of Management November 8, 2001 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - WAC and Old Dominion University Event, National Town December 5, 2001 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - World Quest (I) December 2001 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - World Quest (II) December 2001 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Laurie Garrett, Science Correspondent, Author January 14, 2002 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Great Decisions 2002 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - WAC and Christopher Newport University Event - Carmen Suro-Bredie, Assistant U.S. Trade Representative for Policy Coordination February 21, 2002 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Peter Hakim, President, Inter-American Dialogue February 28, 2002 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - WAC, Norfolk Southern Corporation and Norfolk Sister City Association Event - Alexandre Philon, Ambassador of Greece April 25, 2002 (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Ambassador Ryan C. Crocker, Deputy Assistant May 16, 2002 (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Richard L. Jachne, Colonel (USMC Ret.), Governor's Terrorism Task Force, Illinois June 6, 2002 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - WAC and The Navy League of Hampton Roads Event - Jonathan T. Howe, Admiral (USN Ret.) September 12, 2002 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Sir Christopher Meyer, Ambassador of Great Britain October 10, 2002 (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Mark Malloch Brown October 22, 2002 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - United Nations Week October 22-26, 2002 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - WAC and Economics Club of Hampton Roads Event - Frank A. Cappiello, President, McCollough, Andrews & Cappiello, Inc. November 13, 2002 (Box-folder 28:8)
    - World Quest November 2002 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - World Quest Silent Auction November 2002 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - WAC and WHRO Event - Kevin Klose, President and CEO, National Public Radio January 9, 2003 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Great Decisions (I) 2003 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Great Decisions (II) 2003 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - US and Asia: What Does the Future Hold? January 29-February 1 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Ambassador Chas W. Freeman, President, Middle East Policy Council, Co-Chair, U.S. China Policy Foundation February 6, 2003 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Mitchell B. Reiss, Director, Reves Center for International Studies March 6, 2003 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Azalea Festival, Robert Bradtke April 24, 2003 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Steven J. McCormick, President and CEO, The Nature Conservancy May 15, 2003 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Daniel Yergin and Andy Kohut June 23, 2003 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission - Poland September 7-14, 2003 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Admiral and Ambassador Joseph W. Prueher, Former Commander, U.S. Pacific Command and Former U.S. Ambassador to the People's Republic of China September 9, 2003 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Ambassador Thomas D. Boyatt, President, Foreign Affairs Council and Board of Governor's, American Foreign Policy Association October 2, 2003 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission Bulletin - Jordan October 12-18, 2003 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - Melinda L. Kimple October 22, 2003 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - United Nations Week October 22-24, 2003 (Box 30:9)
    - WAC and Economics Club of Hampton Roads Event - Itaru Shimazu, Dean, Graduate School of Social Studies and Law, Chiba University, Tokyo November 7, 2003 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - World Quest 2003 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - World Quest Brochure - Ads 2003 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - World Quest - Donations 2003 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - World Quest - Information 2003 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - World Quest - Invoices 2003 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - World Quest - Participation 2003 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - World Quest - Reservations 2003 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - World Quest - Silent Auction (I) 2003 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - World Quest - Silent Auction (II) 2003 (Box-folder 31:9)
    - World Quest - Team Standings 2003 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - World Quest - Thank You Letters 2003 (Box-folder 31:11)
    - World Quest - Webb Center 2003 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Ambassador Richard D. Kauzlarich, National Intelligence Officer, Europe January 15, 2004 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Corporate Sponsor Campaign Lunch January 27, 2004 (Box-folder 32:3)
    - Great Decisions (I) 2004 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - Great Decisions (II) 2004 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - WAC and Alliance Française Event - Jean-David Levitte - Ambassador of the Republic of Franc February 19, 2004 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - José A. Fourquet - United States Executive Director of the Inter- American Development Bank March 10, 2004 (Box-folder 32:7)
    - Azalea Festival 2004 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - Amb. Marc Grossman - WAC 35th Anniversary May 20, 2004 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Dr. Haifa Reda Jamal Al Lail - President, Effat College, Jeddah, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia June 9, 2004 (Box-folder 33:3)
    - Dr. Khaled A. Al-Maeena, Editor in Chief, Arab News, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia September 16, 2004 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - Philip Merrill, President and Chairman, Export-Import Bank of the United States October 28, 2004 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - World Quest (I) 2004 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - World Quest (II) 2004 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Carmen Suro-Bredie December 1, 2004 (Box-folder 34:1)